Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Czechoslovakia, 13
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - AI saved my life''., 10/1983; D57 (Microfiche 42)
    - Rudolf Battek., 10/1983; D58 (Microfiche 42)
    - Ivan Jirous (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 2/1984; D59 (Microfiche 48)
    - Czechoslovak driver who told about prison gets six years., 5/1984; D60 (Microfiche 48)
    - Tough surveillance restrictions on released'' prisoners., 6/1984; D61 (Microfiche 48)
    - Prisoners of conscience., 8/1984; D62 (Microfiche 48)
    - Jaroslav Javorsky (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 7/1985; D63 (Microfiche 57)
    - Slovak Catholics imprisoned., 8/1985; D64 (Microfiche 57)
    - Ivan Jirous (Prisoners of the Month 1984)., 9/1985; D65 (Microfiche 57)
    - Czechoslovakia: Prisoners released in 1985., 1/1986; D66 (Microfiche 66)
    - Czechoslovakia: Human rights activist released., 2/1986; D67 (Microfiche 66)
    - Czechoslovakia: Religious believers arrested., 3/1986; D68 (Microfiche 66)
    - Czechoslovakia: Pavel Krivka and Pavel Skoda. (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 7/1986; D69 (Microfiche 66)
    - Czechoslovakia: Jaroslav Javorsky (Prisoners of the Month 1985)., 8/1986; D70 (Microfiche 66)
    - Czechoslovakia: Prisoners of conscience., 11/1986; D71 (Microfiche 66)
    - Trials in Czechoslovakia., 5/1987; D72 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Ervin Motl (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 6/1987; D73 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Pavel Skoda and Pavel Krivka (Prisoners of the Month 1986: Update)., 8/1987; D74 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Ervin Motl., 2/1988; Amnesty International focus: Human rights now!; D75 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia: Ervin Motl, Pavel Krivka., 7/1988; Focus on Prisoners of the Month (1987).; D76 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia: Activists jailed in crackdown., 5/1989; D77 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: Frantisek Starek: the 36-year-old editor of an unofficial cultural magazine entitled Vokno (Window), was sentenced to 30 months' imprisonment to be followed by two years' protective surveillance'' by a court in Usti nad Orlici on 28 June. He had been in custody since 23 February 1989. (Campaign for Prisoners of the Month)., 8/1989; D78 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: former prisoners in government., 2/1990; D79 (Microfiche 110)
    - Czechoslovakia: Picture of Vaclev Havel, former prisoner of conscience., 9/1991; Amnesty International Newsletter, September 1991 (30th Anniversary Focus).; D80 (Microfiche 119)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Letter to Dr. Gustav Husak, President, from families of prisoners: request for the release of Czech political prisoners, complaint about inhuman and illegal conditions to which they are subjected., 1/3/1976; E1 (Microfiche 2)
    - Text of an article Comment on a provocation'' from Rude Pravo - 26/10/76., 17/11/1976; E2 (Microfiche 2)
    - Forthcoming trial of Czechoslovak non- conformist artists., 6/1/1977; (EUR 16/01/77); E3 (Microfiche 2)
    - Recent political trials in Czechoslovakia., 7/11/1977; (EUR 16/06/77); E4 (Microfiche 2)
    - Charter 77: human rights movement in Czechoslovakia., 1/1978; (EUR 16/01/78); E5 (Microfiche 2)
    - Czech Republic: Death in custody., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E6 (Microfiche 187)
    - Czech Republic: The case of Martin Cervenak; ratifications., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E7 (Microfiche 187)
    - Information on prisoners of conscience in Czechoslovakia., 8/1978; (EUR 16/06/78); E8 (Microfiche 3)
    - Charter 77 document no. 16., 1/12/1978; (EUR 16/11/78); E9 (Microfiche 3)
    - Focus on workers and trade unionists in prison. (Extract), 3/1979; (ACT 73/03/79); E10 (Microfiche 3)
    - 11 Czechoslovak human rights activists face heavy sentences., 9/8/1979; (EUR 16/09/79); E11 (Microfiche 3)
    - Official Czechoslovak criticism of Amnesty International., 7/12/1979; (EUR 16/13/79); E12 (Microfiche 3)
    - Trials of members of the Committee for the Defence of the Unjustly Persecuted (VONS) in Czechoslovakia., 15/1/1980; (EUR 16/04/80); E13 (Microfiche 22)
    - Lists of Czechoslovak citizens serving prison sentences whose cases Amnesty International has taken up as Prisoners of Conscience., 4/1980; (EUR 16/06/80); E14 (Microfiche 22)
    - Charter 77: report on conditions in the Corrective Educational Institution (NVU) Plzen-Bory., 30/5/1980; (EUR 16/08/80); E15 (Microfiche 22)
    - Amnesty International reply to official Czechoslovak criticism., 17/11/1980; (EUR 16/17/80); E16 (Microfiche 22)
    - Czech Republic., 1 March 2000; Europe: Concerns in Europe July-December 1999.; (EUR 01/01/00); E16 (Microfiche 285)
    - Prison term extended for insulting public functionary''., 3/1981; Trade union bulletin no. 10.; (ACT 73/01/81); E17 (Microfiche 31)
    - Amnesty International observer excluded from Battek trial., 12/8/1981; Weekly update service 22/81.; (NWS 01/24/81); E18 (Microfiche 31)
    - Petr Uhl., 9/10/1981; Prisoners of Conscience Week 1981.; (ACT 31/02/81); E19 (Microfiche 31)
    - Czechoslovak citizen's letter about Amnesty International to Rude Pravo., 28/1/1982; (EUR 16/01/82); E21 (Microfiche 32)
    - Five workers jailed., 3/1982; Trade union bulletin no. 13.; (ACT 73/01/82); E22 (Microfiche 32)
    - Releases., 31/3/1982; Weekly update service 12/82.; (NWS 01/12/82); E23 (Microfiche 32)
    - Jiri Ruml., 26/4/1982; (EUR 16/07/82); E24 (Microfiche 32)
    - Summary of the official commentary to chapter one of the Czechoslovak Penal Code., 12/5/1982; (EUR 16/08/82); E25 (Microfiche 32)
    - Imprisonment of religious believers in the CSSR., 16/5/1982; (EUR 16/09/82); E26 (Microfiche 32)
    - Zbynek Cerovsky., 19/5/1982; (EUR 16/10/1982); E27 (Microfiche 32)
    - Supreme Court rejects appeals of Charter 77 prisoners., 11/1982; Trade union bulletin no. 15.; (ACT 73/07/82); E28 (Microfiche 32)
    - Petr Pospichal., 3/1983; International action for workers and trade unionists in prison on International Labour Day 1983.; (ACT 73/03/83); E29 (Microfiche 42)
    - Jiri Gruntorad., 3/1983; International action for workers and trade unionists in prison on International Labour Day 1983.; (ACT 73/03/83); E30 (Microfiche 42)
    - Zbynek Cerovsky., 24/3/1983; (EUR 16/09/83); E31 (Microfiche 42)
    - The cases of seven Czechoslovak prisoners of conscience., 11/5/1983; (EUR 16/11/83); E32 (Microfiche 42)
    - Gruntorad beaten and then charged with false accusation''., 7/1983; Trade union bulletin no. 17.; (ACT 73/05/83); E33 (Microfiche 42)
    - Jaromir Savrda., 6/9/1983; (EUR 16/15/83); E34 (Microfiche 42)
    - Rudolf Battek., 17/10/1983; Prisoner of Conscience Week. Human rights activists in prison: Special appeal cases.; (ACT 31/03/83); E35 (Microfiche 42)
    - Jiri Gruntorad transferred to stricter prison regime., 1/1984; Trade union bulletin no. 19.; (ACT 73/02/84); E36 (Microfiche 48)
    - The death penalty in Czechoslovakia., 17/2/1984; (EUR 16/01/84); E37 (Microfiche 48-49)
    - Jaromir Savrda. Follow-up to medical letter- writing action., 12/3/1984; (EUR 16/02/84); E38 (Microfiche 49)
    - Worker accused of anti-state'' activity., 4/1984; Union bulletin no. 20.; (ACT 73/11/84); E39 (Microfiche 49)
    - Jan Keller., 9/5/1984; (EUR 16/05/84); E40 (Microfiche 49)
    - Josef Kajnek., 10/5/1984; (EUR 16/06/84); E41 (Microfiche 49)
    - Jiri Gruntorad sentenced to a further 14 months' imprisonment., 7/1984; Trade union bulletin no. 21.; (ACT 73/15/84); E42 (Microfiche 49)
    - Josef Kajnek., 30/8/1984; (EUR 16/11/84); E43 (Microfiche 49)
    - Jiri Wolf., 22/10/1984; (EUR 16/12/84); E44 (Microfiche 49)
    - Intolerance and discrimination on grounds of religion or belief. (Extract), 11/1984; (POL 03/05/84); E45 (Microfiche 49)
    - Jiri Gruntorad released., 1/1985; Trade union bulletin no. 23.; (ACT 73/02/85); E46 (Microfiche 57)
    - Jiri Wolf., 27/2/1985; International Labour Day Action 1985: special appeal cases.; (ACT 04/08/85); E47 (Microfiche 57)
    - Czechoslovak human rights activists under protection surveillance., 13/8/1985; (EUR 16/13/85); E48 (Microfiche 57)
    - Czechoslovakia., 4/1986; The imprisonment of persons seeking to leave a country or to return to their own country.; (POL 03/02/86); E49 (Microfiche 66)
    - Czechoslovkia., 5/1986; Religious Intolerance.; (POL 03/03/86); E50 (Microfiche 66)
    - Amnesty International concerns in Czechoslovakia., 19/6/1986; (EUR 16/03/86); E51 (Microfiche 67)
    - Imprisonment in Czechoslovakia for the non-violent exercise of the right to freedom of expression., 10/9/1986; (EUR 16/04/86); E52 (Microfiche 67)
    - Medical concern Czechoslovakia: Jiri Wolf., 4/12/1986; (EUR 16/08/86); E53 (Microfiche 67)
    - Human rights activist in poor health. Jazz musicians arrested., 1/1987; Trade Union Bulletin 31.; (ACT 73/01/87); E54 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Trials postponed., 27/3/1987; Weekly Update Service 09/87.; (NWS 01/09/87); E55 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Musicians sent to prison; prisoner of conscience rearrested., 4/1987; Trade Union Bulletin 32.; (ACT 73/04/87); E56 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Update., 8/1987; Trade Union Bulletin 33.; (ACT 73/05/87); E57 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Jiri Wolf., 12/1987; Human Rights Now! Campaign 1988, appeal cases of human rights activists.; (ACT 03/04/87); E58 (Microfiche 77)
    - Czechoslovakia: Firefighters sentenced for exercizing freedom of expression / Musician out of prison., 1/1988; Trade Union Bulletin 35.; (ACT 73/01/88); E59 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia., 2/1988; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/88); E60 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia: Ervin Motl., 3/3/1988; International Labour Day Action 1988 appeal Cases.; (ACT 73/03/88); E61 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia: Prisoner released., 4/1988; Trade Union Bulletin 36.; (ACT 73/05/88); E62 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia: Jiri Wolf., 8/1988; AI Week 1988: Appeal cases of human rights activists.; (ACT 31/01/88); E63 (Microfiche 87)
    - Czechoslovakia: Vaclav Havel released., 18/5/1989; Weekly Update Service 20/89.; (NWS 11/20/89); E64 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: Frantisek Starek, editor of unofficial cultural magazine, prisoner of conscience facing up to five years' imprisonment., 7/1989; Writers and Journalists action 1989.; (ACT 78/02/89); E65 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: Jan Subrt, 21-year-old miner, detained for conscientious objection to military service., 7/1989; Trade Union Bulletin 41.; (ACT 73/08/89); E66 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: Petr Cibulka, music-loving worker in detention, is prisoner of conscience., 10/1989; Trade Union Bulletin 42.; (ACT 73/11/89); E67 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: Current prisoners of conscience., 9/1989; (EUR 16/08/89); E68 (Microfiche 97)
    - Czechoslovakia: Frantisek Starek released 26 November 1989., 5/1990; Update to Writers and Journalists Action: July 1989.; (ACT 78/01/90); E69 (Microfiche 110)
    - Ireland and Czech and Slovak Republic abolish death penalty., 12/9/1990; Death Penalty News.; (ACT 53/05/90); E70 (Microfiche 110)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic., 1/1991; Conscientious objection to military service.; (POL 31/01/91); E71 (Microfiche 119)
    - Czech and Slovak Federative Republic., 30/1/1991; The death penalty: list of abolitionist and retentionist countries.; (ACT 50/01/91); E72 (Microfiche 119)
    - Czech and Slovak Federative Republic., 6/1991; Concerns in Europe: November 1990 -April 1991.; (EUR 01/01/91); E73 (Microfiche 119)
    - Czech and Slovak Republic: International treaties., 10/1991; Death Penalty News.; (ACT 53/04/91); E74 (Microfiche 119)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic: Amnesty International writes to government about conscientious objection legislation., 23/10/1991; Weekly Update Service 40/91.; (NWS 11/40/91); E75 (Microfiche 119)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic: Totally abolitionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E76 (Microfiche 134)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic: concern over provisions restricting freedom of expression., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E77 (Microfiche 134)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic: alleged ill-treatment of Roma in Lomnicka; ill-treatment of spectators at football match; law restricting freedom of expression amended by the Constitutional Court., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E78 (Microfiche 134)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic: ratifications., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E79 (Microfiche 134)
    - Czech and Slovak Federal Republic and Hungary ratify the Sixth Protocol., 12/1992; Death Penalty News: December 1992.; (ACT 53/05/92); E80 (Microfiche 134)
- Denmark, 14
  - Publications, A
    - Denmark., 1989; Country survey section of When the State Kills ...'' The Death Penalty v. Human Rights.; (ACT 51/07/89); A1 (Microfiche 97)
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Denmark., 1991; Amnesty International Report 1991.; (POL 10/01/91); B1 (Microfiche 119)
    - Denmark., 9/7/1992; Amnesty International Report 1992.; (POL 10/01/92); B2 (Microfiche 134)
    - Denmark., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B3 (Microfiche 151)
    - Denmark., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B4 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B5 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B6 (Microfiche 207)
    - Denmark., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B7 (Microfiche 226)
    - Denmark., 17 June 1998; Amnesty International Report 1998.; (POL 10/01/98); B8 (Microfiche 245)
    - Denmark., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B9 (Microfiche 350)
  - News releases, C
    - Denmark: Amnesty International welcomes ratification against the death penalty., 1 March 1994; Amnesty International News Service 39/94.; (NWS 11/39/94); C1 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International delegation meets minister of justice., 25 May 1994; Amnesty International News Service 108/94.; (NWS 11/108/94); C2 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International calls on Danish authorities to stop police ill-treatment., 21 June 1994; Amnesty International News Service 122/94.; (NWS 11/122/94); C3 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International challenges police to respond to recommendations on ill-treatment., 22 June 1994; AI News Service 131/94.; (NWS 11/131/94); C4 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International welcomes suspension of leg-lock., 27 June 1994; Amnesty International News Service 137/94.; (NWS 11/137/94); C5 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International reiterates call for independent inquiry into police ill-treatment., 21 July 1994; Amnesty International News Service 159/94.; (NWS 11/159/94); C6 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Publication of report by Director of Public Prosecution., 26 August 1994; AI News Service 199/94.; (NWS 11/199/94); C7 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International has not retracted concerns about ill-treatment., 14 September 1994; Amnesty International News Service 209/94.; (NWS 11/209/94); C8 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International welcomes recommendation that Mrs Anderson'' be paid compensation., 8 March 1995; Amnesty International News Service 48/95.; (NWS 11/48/95); C9 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark: UN Committee against torture review of government report., 10 November 1995; (EUR 18/02/95); C10 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International welcomes Christiania investigation., 20 November 1995; (EUR 18/03/95); C11 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International welcomes initiatives following Christiania investigation., 21 November 1995; (EUR 18/04/95); C12 (Microfiche 187)
    - Israel and the Occupied Territories/Denmark: Amnesty International calls on Denmark to fulfill its obligations under the UN Convention against Torture., 14 August 2001; (MDE 15/74/01); C13 (Microfiche 306)
    - Denmark: Amnesty International calls on Danish EU presidency to take concrete action to eradicate torture., 28 June 2002; (EUR 18/01/02); C14 (Microfiche 326)
    - Russian Federation: Amnesty International calls for assurances on Zakayev case., 30 October 2002; (EUR 46/57/02); C15 (Microfiche 326)
    - Denmark/Iraq: International Justice for the victims of Halabja., 22 November 2002; (EUR 18/02/02); C16 (Microfiche 326)
    - Russian Federation: Denmark releases Chechen envoy., 3 December 2002; (EUR 46/65/02); C17 (Microfiche 326)
    - USA/UK/Denmark: Release of detainees., 19 February 2004; (AMR 51/37/04); C18 (Microfiche 375)
  - Newsletter entries, D
    - Denmark ratifies optional protocol., 1 May 1994; AI Newsletter May 1994.; (NWS 21/05/94); D1 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Wide-ranging ill-treatment by police., 1 August 1994; AI Newsletter August 1994.; (NWS 21/08/94); D2 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: News in brief., 1 March 1995; Amnesty International Newsletter March 1995.; (NWS 21/03/95); D3 (Microfiche 187)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - The death penalty in Western Europe. (Extract), 15/6/1984; (EUR 01/01/84); E1 (Microfiche 49)
    - Denmark., 28/5/1986; The death penalty in Western Europe.; (EUR 03/02/86); E2 (Microfiche 67)
    - Denmark (Faroe Islands)., 10/1986; AI's concerns in Western Europe. March 1986 - September 1986.; (EUR 03/06/86); E3 (Microfiche 67)
    - Denmark., 8/1987; The death penalty in Western Europe (Revised Edition August 1987).; (EUR 03/02/87); E4 (Microfiche 77)
    - Denmark., 11/1990; Western Europe: Concerns May - October 1990.; (EUR 03/02/90); E5 (Microfiche 110)
    - Denmark: allegations of ill treatment: the cases of Hamad Hassan Juma and Babading Fatty., 6/1991; Concerns in Europe November 1990 to April 1991.; (EUR 01/01/91); E6 (Microfiche 120)
    - Denmark: Report of the European Committee for the Prevention of Torture., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E7 (Microfiche 120)
    - Denmark: Totally abolitionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E8 (Microfiche 134)
    - Denmark: allegations of ill-treatment - the cases of Himid Hassan Juma and Babading Fatty., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E9 (Microfiche 134)
    - Denmark: Allegations of ill-treatment in police custody., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E10 (Microfiche 134)
    - Amnesty International visits Denmark., 15 June 1993; Weekly Update Service 61/93.; (NWS 11/61/93); E11 (Microfiche 151)
    - Denmark: Shootings at a demonstration; allegations of ill-treatment., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E12 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark ratifies the Scond Optional Protocol to the International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights., 1 March 1994; Death Penalty News March 1994.; (ACT 53/01/94); E13 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Death penalty; shootings at a demonstration; allegations of ill-treatment; ratifications., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1994 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E14 (Microfiche 169)
    - Denmark: Police ill-treatment., 21 June 1994; (EUR 18/01/94); E15 (Microfiche 169-170)
    - Police ill-treatment in Denmark: a summary of Amnesty International's concerns., 21 June 1994; (EUR 18/02/94); E16 (Microfiche 170)
    - Medical letter writing action: Denmark: physical restraint., 4 July 1994; (EUR 18/05/94); E17 (Microfiche 170)
    - Denmark: Concerns regarding alleged ill-treatment., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E18 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark: Developments on Amnesty International's concerns., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E19 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark: Comments by Amnesty International in conjunction with the examination of the government's Second Periodic Report to the United Nations Committee against Torture., 1 October 1995; (EUR 18/01/95); E20 (Microfiche 187)
    - Denmark., 1 March 1996; Concerns in Europe July - December 1995.; (EUR 01/01/96); E21 (Microfiche 207)
    - Denmark., 1 March 1997; Concerns in Europe July - December 1996.; (EUR 01/01/97); E22 (Microfiche 226)
    - Denmark., 19 March 1997; Bosnia-Herzegovina: Who's living in my house?'': Obstacles to the safe return of refugees and displaced people.; (EUR 63/01/97); E23 (Microfiche 226)
    - Denmark: Ill-treatment allegations., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January -June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E24 (Microfiche 226)
    - Denmark: Fining of Carriers by EU Member States., 1 October 1997; No Flights To Safety: Carrier Sanctions; Airline Employees and the Rights of Refugees.; (ACT 34/21/97); E25 (Microfiche 226)
    - Denmark: Alleged ill-treatment., 1 February 1998; Concerns in Europe, July - December 1997.; (EUR 01/01/98); E26 (Microfiche 245)
    - Federal Republic of Yugoslavia: Still forgotten: An update on conscientious objectors after the Kosovo conflict., 19 June 2000; (EUR 70/28/00); E27 (Microfiche 285)
    - Denmark., 1 September 2002; Concerns in Europe January - June 2002.; (EUR 01/07/02); E28 (Microfiche 326)
- Estonia, 15
  - Annual Report entry, B
    - Estonia., 9/7/1992; Amnesty International Report 1992.; (POL 10/01/92); B1 (Microfiche 134)
    - Estonia., 1 July 1993; Amnesty International Report 1993.; (POL 10/01/93); B2 (Microfiche 151)
    - Estonia., 7 July 1994; Amnesty International Report 1994.; (POL 10/02/94); B3 (Microfiche 170)
    - Estonia., 1 July 1995; Amnesty International Report 1995.; (POL 10/01/95); B4 (Microfiche 187)
    - Estonia., 18 June 1996; Amnesty International Report 1996.; (POL 10/02/96); B5 (Microfiche 207)
    - Estonia., 18 June 1997; Amnesty International Report 1997.; (POL 10/01/97); B6 (Microfiche 226)
    - Estonia., 28 May 2003; Amnesty International Report 2003.; (POL 10/003/03); B7 (Microfiche 350)
    - Estonia., 26 May 2004; Amnesty International Report 2004.; (POL 10/04/04); B8 (Microfiche 375)
    - Estonia., 25 May 2005; Amnesty International Report 2005.; (POL 10/001/2005); B9 (Microfiche 399)
  - News releases, C
    - Estonia: No action yet taken on detained asylum seekers., 3 October 1994; AI News Service 230/94.; (NWS 11/230/94); C1 (Microfiche 170)
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Estonia: Concern over provisions for conscientious objectors to military service; the death penalty; ratification of international human rights instruments., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E1 (Microfiche 120)
    - Estonia: Retentionist., 2/1992; Europe: Moving towards complete abolition of the death penalty.; (EUR 01/01/92); E1 (Microfiche 134)
    - Estonia: ratifications., 11/1991; Concerns in Europe May - October 1991.; (EUR 01/02/91); E2 (Microfiche 120)
    - Estonia: the death penalty; ratification of international human rights instruments., 6/1992; Amnesty International concerns in Europe November 1991 - April 1992.; (EUR 01/03/92); E2 (Microfiche 134)
    - Estonia: Moves towards abolition., 6/1992; Death Penalty News June 1992.; (ACT 53/03/92); E3 (Microfiche 134)
    - The Baltic States: Amnesty International visits Estonia, Latvia and Lithuania., 8/10/1992; Weekly Update Service 40/92.; (NWS 11/40/92); E4 (Microfiche 134)